0539-987-0836

MERT OKAN

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

mertokan5020@gmail.com

https://mertokan.vercel.app

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mert-okan/

About Me

I am a developer with more than I year of Front-end Development experience. I have an intermediate level of knowledge in basic technologies like HTML, CSS, JavaScript and ReactJS. My goal is to improve user experience and create impressive web applications. I want to gain more experience in the field of Front-end Development and continue to improve myself by doing projects. I am always ready to collaborate and learn.

Projects

Portfolio Website Github:

Aug 2023 - Present https://github.com/Elitesmert/Portfolio-v1.0

The website with information about me. ReactJs, ViteJS, Tailwind CSS were used on the site.

Weather App Github:

Sep 2023 - Sep 2023 https://github.com/Elitesmert/weather-app

I made a weather application that can draw api with axios.

ATB Website Github:

Aug 2023 - Oct 2023 https://github.com/Elitesmert/atb

A project I made for my friends. A site where the group is introduced and applications are received. It is actively used. NextJs, Tailwind CSS were used on the site.

Employment History

Cevher Jant Sanayii A.Ş.

Oct 2020 - Feb 2021

Izmir

Digitalisation

Application development was made to increase efficiency within the factory. The technologies we use are Kuika and Microsoft SQL Server.

Interships

Cevher Jant Sanayii A.Ş.

Sep 2020 - Sep 2020

lzmir

Application development was made to increase efficiency within the factory. The technologies we use are Kuika and Microsoft SQL Server.

Education

Izmir Economy University

Sep 2019 - Oct 2021

Izmir

Computer Programming

Anadolu University

Associate's degree

Sep 2022 - Present

Eskisehir

Licentiate degree

Management Information Systems

Certificate	Extended Software Specialization Training Istanbul Nisantasi University			Oct 2022 - Jul 2023 Istanbul	
Skills	React Tailv	wind CSS CSS	Git	HTML	Javascript
Languages	Turkish	Native speaker	English		В1
Reference	Orhan EKİCİ	Company Zero Studios		Phone 0541-304	4-5074